flyairpeace.com 2019-12-28

# Privacy Policy | flyairpeace.com

By Personal information or data we mean information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, your name, title, gender, birth date, email address, telephone number, a home, postal or other physical address, other contact information, other information that can be used to identify you.

When you visit our website, you do so anonymously. We do not automatically collect personal information, including your email address(es). Air Peace may however request for certain personal information such as your name, address, telephone numbers, fax numbers, email address and/or debit/credit card details including billing address, passport number and nationality for the purpose of rendering a service you have requested to you or fulfilling an obligation such as making a reservation, registering an account on or utilizing our Peace Advantage promotions, a subscription to our newsletter, a registration to an event, participating in an online survey or when you ask to be included in an email as well as other mailing list, etc .

We may likewise request your specific medical condition where essential. Our general terms of carriage will have provided a detail of when this will be essential. At all times, this information will be requested for your safety and to serve you better.

Personal information provided on Air Peace website are only used and processed to the extent necessary for us to fulfill our obligations to you, and/or to comply with our legal obligations.

There are circumstances where we may have to collect personal information about you from a third party such as a person making a booking on your account. It is deemed, in such circumstances that you have consented to your personal information being collected by us and to us handling it in accordance with this Policy. Notify us as soon as you come to the knowledge that your personal data has been provided to us by someone who does not have your consent to deal with it in that manner.
